- The biggest things we achieve at work
-我們在工作中實現的最大事情
often start as an idea.
通常從一個想法開始。
But the journey from a spark of inspiration
但是，從靈感的火花
to a finished project isn't easy.
到完成項目的旅程並不容易。
Identifying the right solution, building a plan,
找出正確的解決方案，制定計劃
and, you know, managing all the bumps along the way?
，您知道，管理過程中的所有障礙？
That can feel like a lot.
這可能感覺很多。
But what if you had a new partner in this process?
但是，如果你在這個過程中有一個新的合作夥伴怎麼辦？
A creative collaborator to help you generate possibilities,
一位創意協作者可幫助您創造可能性
a master strategist to stress test your assumptions,
，一位大師來壓力測試您的假設，以
and an execution expert
及一位
to build a plan based on your ideas to get the job done?
根據您的想法構建計劃來完成工作的執行專家？
Hi, my name is Yul.
嗨，我叫尤爾。
I'm a VPO of Product Management at Google,
我是 Google 產品管理的 VPO，並協助領導一
and I help lead a research team
個名為「智能模範」的研
called Paradigms of Intelligence,
究團隊，該研究團隊
which tries to understand
試圖了解智能
the nature and building blocks of intelligence.
的性質和構成部分。
Now, in this course, we'll show you how Gemini can be
現在，在本課程中，我們將向您展示雙子座如何
that creative partner for you
成為您的創意夥伴
so that you can think big and achieve your goals at work.
，以便您可以大思考並在工作中實現目標。
First, you'll learn techniques to generate ideas with you.
首先，您將學習與您一起產生想法的技術。
We'll simulate experts and push creative boundaries
我們將模擬專家並突破創意界限
to uncover solutions you never would've considered.
，發現您從未考慮過的解決方案。
And we'll show you how you can use Gemini
我們將向您展示如何使用 Gemini 將行
to bring industry knowledge into the process to help.
業知識帶入過程中，以提供幫助。
Next, you'll pressure test solutions.
接下來，您將進行壓力測試解決方案。
Now, the best ideas are ones
現在，最好的想法是
that can stand up to potential problems in the future.
能夠應對未來潛在問題的想法。
But spotting those problems before they happen can be tough.
但是在發生之前發現這些問題可能很難。
You'll learn to use Gemini as a devil's advocate
您將學會使用雙子座作為魔鬼的倡導者，在策
to find risks in your strategy before they become problems.
略中發現風險之前，在它們成為問題之前找到風險。
You'll also learn how to apply constraints
您還將學習如何應用約束
to get to the most relevant solutions
以獲得最相關的解決方案
so that you can choose the best path.
，以便您可以選擇最佳路徑。
Finally, you'll manage your project
最後，您將通過讓所有人掌握
by getting everyone on the same page.
相同的頁面來管理您的項目。
We'll show you how to use NotebookLM
我們將向您展示如何使用 NotebookLM
to create an information hub
建立資訊中心，您
where you and your teammates can ask questions
和您的團隊成員可以在幾秒鐘內提出問
and get answers about the project in literally seconds.
題並獲得有關專案的答案。
It all sounds pretty great, right?
這一切聽起來都很棒，對吧？
Well, it kind of is.
好吧，有點是。
But to make this a reality,
但為了實現這一目標，
you'll also need to understand some key principles
您還需要了解有效
for using AI effectively.
使用 AI 的一些關鍵原則。
But, don't worry, we've got you covered.
但是，不用擔心，我們為您提供幫助。
First up is problem framing.
首先是問題框架。
Before you even consider using AI,
在考慮使用 AI 之前，
you need to clearly define
您需要清楚地
the problem you're trying to solve and why.
定義要解決的問題以及原因。
Where you are and where you want to go
您所在的位置和您想去的地
will anchor the process from start to finish.
方將從頭到尾固定過程。
You also provide essential context.
您還提供基本的背景。
Now, AI doesn't have all the background information
現在，AI 不具有關
about your customers, your team dynamics,
客戶、團隊動態
or your leadership's priorities.
或領導者優先事項的所有背景資訊。
Those are the critical things
這些是決定要採取哪
that determine which solutions to pursue
些解決方案以及應該添
and what steps should be added to your project plan.
加哪些步驟到您的項目計劃中的關鍵因素。
And that information can only come from you.
而這些信息只能來自您。
Throughout this process,
在整個過程
you're setting up the problem, exploring the options,
中，您正在設置問題，探索選項，
and using your judgment
並使用自己
to make a decision on what to do next.
的判斷決定接下一步做什麼。
Now, AI isn't perfect,
現在，AI 並不完
and it can sometimes give you ideas
美，而且有時會給
that won't be a good fit.
您不合適的想法。
So, please, be a tough critic.
所以，請成為一個強烈的評論家。
With this new way of working,
有了這種新的工作方式
you'll have a resource to turn to
，您幾乎可以在專案
at almost every stage of the project lifecycle,
生命週期的每個階段使用資源，
from idea to plan to delivery.
從想法到計劃到交付。
It's a mindset shift.
這是一個心態轉變。
And, by the end of this course,
此外，在本課程結束時，
you'll be able to break through creative blocks,
您將能夠突破創意塊，為複
find unexpected solutions to complicated problems,
雜問題找到意外
and turn your best ideas into action plans
的解決方案，並將您的最佳想法轉化為推動進步
that drive progress.
的行動計劃。
So good luck.
所以祝你好運。